bugsplat.com 2019-04-16

# Privacy Policy | BugSplat

## BugSplat Privacy Policy

####  **Last Updated: May 16, 2018**

BugSplat, LLC (“BugSplat”) offers a crash reporting service that provides developers with information about the stability of their applications (the “Services”). This Privacy Policy describes how BugSplat collects, uses and shares information about application developers that are customers of BugSplat (“Developers”) and the end users of their applications (“End Users”) that use our Services. The policy also explains how BugSplat collects and uses information when individuals visit our websites. We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy in order to learn more about how we safeguard your privacy.

When using any of our Services you consent to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. Irrespective of which country you reside in or supply information from, you authorize BugSplat to use your information in the United States and any other country where we operate.

###  ** _SCOPE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY_**

Section 1 of this Privacy Policy covers BugSplat’s treatment of information that may be collected from End Users. Section 2 of this Privacy Policy covers BugSplat’s treatment of information collected from Developers using the Services. Section 3 contains information about our privacy practices that applies to both Developers and End Users, including information collected when an individual uses the BugSplat websites.

The policy specifically addresses the following areas:

  * What information is collected by the BugSplat websites and Services;
  * How BugSplat uses this information;
  * With whom BugSplat may share this information;
  * What choices are available to you with respect to collection and use of information collected by BugSplat;
  * What types of security procedures are in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control; and
  * How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information we hold about you.

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies not owned or controlled by BugSplat (including Developers) or to people whom BugSplat does not employ or manage.

####  **SECTION 1: END USER INFORMATION**

This Section provides information on the collection and use of information from End Users.

 **What information does BugSplat collect from End Users?**

The Services collect certain information that does not personally identify End Users who access or use applications that use the Services. This information includes, but is not limited to, computer state information, information relating to how an application functions, and the type of computer hardware and operating system being used.

Developers may also use certain features of the Services that will allow BugSplat to collect some End Users’ personally identifiable information and feedback that End Users voluntarily provide. For example, end users may provide BugSplat with their email addresses so that the Developers can contact them. BugSplat captures all of this information on Developers’ behalf so that they can understand and improve their applications and communicate with users about their experience with the applications. BugSplat requires Developers to use BugSplat to collect information solely for these purposes, and to observe all applicable laws and regulations.

 **How does BugSplat use the information that it collects?**

The information BugSplat collects about End Users and their activities is the property of the Developer, not of BugSplat. The information collected by the Services from End Users is used to provide Developers with insight into the functionality of and engagement with their applications, including any problems that occur. Our algorithms process and analyze the data separately for each Developer, so if you are an End User of multiple Developers that are BugSplat’s customers your information is not shared across Developers. However, BugSplat does aggregate information across Developers in a non-personally identifiable way. Such aggregate and anonymous information is used by BugSplat to (i) improve the Services, (ii) create analysis of trends or behaviors and (iii) other similar uses, but always in an aggregate and anonymous way.

 **Will BugSplat share information about me with anyone else?**

Except as provided below in Section 3, we never divulge End User data to anyone other than the Developer on whose behalf we are collecting and analyzing its End User data.

 **Is there a way that End Users can opt out of collection of information by BugSplat?**

Collection of information is at the discretion of each Developer, so please consult with the Developer whose application you are using as to how to opt out of collection of information by BugSplat.

####  **SECTION 2: DEVELOPER INFORMATION**

This Section provides information on the collection and use of information from Developers.

 **What information does BugSplat collect from Developers?**

BugSplat collects the following information from Developers:

 _Usage Data:_

BugSplat collects information relating to the usage of the Services from Developers in order to better provide the service to Developers, to improve the performance of the Services generally, and to bill them appropriately for use of the Service.

 _Account Information:_

When you create an account with BugSplat, you will provide us with certain personally identifiable information, such as but not limited to your name, contact information, company name and account user name and password. We recognize that this information is very important to you and we will never divulge any of your personally identifiable information to anyone without your permission except as needed to provide Services to you and as described in Section 3 below.

 **How does BugSplat use the information collected from Developers?**

Our primary goal in collecting information from you is to provide you with a great experience while using our websites and to allow us to provide the Services to you. We use personal information solely for the purpose of contacting you with respect to your use of the Services, providing the Services to you and generally facilitating your use of the Services, or informing you about features of our Services that may be of interest to you.

In order to customize the online user experience, improve the Services generally, and provide Developers with useful statistics and analysis regarding use of the Services, we may use certain aggregate, anonymous information, including, without limitation, Services usage information, for such purpose, but never in a manner in which the Developer or any End User identity is reasonably ascertainable.

 **How can Developers change or delete information?**

You may review, update, correct or delete the personally identifiable information in your BugSplat account where it is inaccurate by contacting us. If you would like us to delete your BugSplat account in our system, please contact us at support@bugsplat.com with a request that we delete your personally identifiable information from our database. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to honor your request. If you request that your personally identifiable information be deleted from our records, there may be a brief delay in our processing that request, while we verify that the request is valid and originates from you as opposed to an unauthorized third party. If you request that your information be deleted, we reserve the right to terminate and/or limit your access to the Services, as we may need such information to provide the Services to you. We may retain an archived copy of your records as required by law or for legitimate business purposes. If your personally identifiable information changes, you may contact us to correct, update or delete and deactivate our record of your personally identifiable information.

####  **SECTION 3: GENERAL INFORMATION**

This Section applies to information collected from End Users and Developers, as well as visitors to the BugSplat website.

What precautions does BugSplat take to ensure the security of information collected?

BugSplat has implemented reasonable security measures in order to protect both personal and nonpersonal information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction.

Under what circumstances will BugSplat share my information with third parties?

Except for the provision of End User information relating to a specific Developer’s application to that Developer as described above, BugSplat will never give your information to, or share your information with, any third party except as provided below (which disclosure shall always be in accordance with applicable law). BugSplat will share information about you only as follows:

  * We may share information with service providers we engage to perform functions and provide services to us in the United States and abroad, subject to confidentiality obligations consistent with this Privacy Policy, and on the condition that the third parties use your information only on our behalf and pursuant to our instructions.
  * We have your consent to share the information.
  * Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in this Privacy Policy, we may disclose information if we believe that it is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical issues; or to protect BugSplat’s rights or property.
  * In the event that BugSplat is involved in a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets, your information may be sold or transferred as part of that transaction. The promises in this Privacy Policy will apply to your information as transferred to the new entity.

 **Does BugSplat collect any information from children?**

Our websites and the Services are not directed to children and BugSplat does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under 13 years of age. If you learn that BugSplat has collected any personally identifiable information from children under 13 years of age, please contact us at support@bugsplat.com.

 **Does BugSplat collect information when I visit the BugSplat websites?**

When you visit our websites, our servers automatically record certain information in our log files. This web log information includes your IP address, browser type, operating system, the referring web page, pages visited, and cookie information (discussed further below). Like many websites, we use web log information, along with cookies and similar technologies, to operate our websites, better understand how they are used, resolve technical problems, and enhance your experience on our websites.

 **Does BugSplat use cookies?**

Yes. Like many companies, BugSplat uses cookies. A cookie is a small text file stored on the customer’s hard drive for an extended period of time, which may include a unique identifier that is sent to a user’s browser from a website’s computer and stored on the user’s computer’s hard drive. The website placing the cookie on the user’s computer can then recognize the computer when the user navigates the website at a later time. We use this information to improve your experience.

Although most web browsers automatically accept cookies, your browser setting can usually be modified to decline cookies or alert you when a website is attempting to place a cookie on your computer. Consult the help manual for your browser for detailed information. If you choose to decline cookies, you may lose some of the functionality associated with the Services or the BugSplat websites.

 **Does BugSplat control Developers or other third parties?**

No. Please be advised that we do not control and are not responsible for the privacy practices of any third party, including, but not limited to, Developers and any website or service that links to or from the BugSplat websites or the Services. While, as discussed above, we require that Developers maintain a privacy policy that fully and accurately discloses their data collection practices, we cannot control the actions of Developers, so please be sure to review the privacy policies of any online services that you may use.

 **BugSplat and GDPR**

If you've entered into a data processing agreement (DPA) with BugSplat you have additional rights

 **Can this Privacy Policy change?**

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make a change to this policy that, in our sole discretion, is material, we will notify you by posting notice of the change on www.BugSplat.com and in this Privacy Policy.

 **Who can I contact if I have questions about this Privacy Policy?**

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy or any other questions about the BugSplat websites or the Services, please contact us at support@bugsplat.com. We will make every effort to resolve your concerns.
